Guide to the Actors' Equity Association Theatrical Programs WAG.257
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series I: New York City, Regional Theatres and Touring Productions/Companies
  - Oliver, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 8)
  - Oliver, Oliver, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 9)
  - On A Clear Day You Can See Forever, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 10)
  - On Borrowed Time, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 11)
  - On Golden Pond, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 12)
  - On the Town, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 13)
  - On the Twentieth Century, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 14)
  - On Whitman Avenue, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 15)
  - On Your Toes, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 16)
  - Once in a Lifetime, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 17)
  - Once on this Island, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 18)
  - Once Upon a Mattress, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 19)
  - Ondine, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 20)
  - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 21)
  - One for the Money, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 22)
  - 110 in the Shade, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 23)
  - One Sunday Afternoon, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 24)
  - One Touch of Venus, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 25)
  - Only Game in Town, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 26)
  - Only in America, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 27)
  - Only Kidding, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 28)
  - Operation Sidewinder, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 29)
  - Oregon Shakespeare Festival, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 30)
  - Orphans, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 31)
  - Orpheus Descending, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 32)
  - Othello, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 33)
  - Other People's Money, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 34)
  - Otherwise Engaged, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 35)
  - Our Town, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 36)
  - Out of this World, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 37)
  - Over Here!, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 38)
  - Over Twenty-One, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 39)
  - Owl and the Pussycat, Undated (Box 34A, Folder 40)
  - P, Undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - P, 1918 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - P, 1920s (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - P, 1930s (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - P, 1940s (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - P, 1950s (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - P (file 1 of 3), 1960s (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - P (file 2 of 3), 1960s (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - P (file 3 of 3), 1960s (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - P (file 1 of 2), 1970s (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - P (file 2 of 2), 1970s (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - P (file 1 of 2), 1980s (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - P (file 2 of 2), 1980s (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - P (file 1 of 2), 1990s (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - P (file 2 of 2), 1990s (Box 35A, Folder 1)
  - P, 2000s (Box 35A, Folder 2)
  - Pacific Overtures, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 3)
  - Pageant, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 4)
  - Paint Your Wagon, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 5)
  - Pajama Game, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 6)
  - Pajama Tops, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 7)
  - Pal Joey, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 8)
  - Panama Hattie, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 9)
  - Pantagleize, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 10)
  - Papa, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 11)
  - Paper Moon, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 12)
  - Paradise Lost, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 13)
  - Park, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 14)
  - Park Your Car in Harvard Yard, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 15)
  - Party with Betty Comden and Adolph Green, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 16)
  - Passing Show of 1914, 1915, 1921, 1923, 1924, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 17)
  - Passion, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 18)
  - Passione, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 19)
  - Past Tense, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 20)
  - Paul Robeson, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 21)
  - Peepshow, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 22)
  - Peer Gynt, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 23)
  - Penny for a Song, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 24)
  - Pennsylvania Shakespeare Festival, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 25)
  - People's Light and Theatre Company, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 26)
  - Perfect Ganish, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 27)
  - Perfect Pitch, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 28)
  - Pericles, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 29)
  - Persecution and Assassination of Marat as Performed by the Inmates of the Asylum of Charenton Under the Direction of the Marquis De Sade, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 30)
  - Personal Appearance, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 31)
  - Peter Pan, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 32)
  - Peterpat, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 33)
  - Petrified Forest, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 34)
  - Phaedra/Phèdre, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 35)
  - Phantom, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 36)
  - Phantom of the Opera, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 37)
  - Philadelphia Here I Come, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 38)
  - Philadelphia Story, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 39)
  - Philanthropist, Undated (Box 35A, Folder 40)
  - Phoenix Too Frequent, Undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Physicists, Undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Piaf, Undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Piano Bar: A Musical, Undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Piano Lesson, Undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Picasso at the Lapine Agile, Undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Pickwick, Undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Picnic, Undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Pictures in the Hallway, Undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Piece of My Heart, Undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Pieces of 8, Undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Pincchio, Undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Pins and Needles, Undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Pippin, Undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Pirate, Undated (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Pirates of Penzance, Undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Place for Polly, Undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Plain and Fancy, Undated (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Platinum, Undated (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Play and Other Plays, Undated (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Play it Again, Sam, Undated (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Play Me a Country Song, Undated (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Play Strindberg, Undated (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Playboy of the Western World, Undated (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Playmakers Repertory Company, Undated (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Play's the Thing, Undated (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Plaza Suite, Undated (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Pleasure of His Company, Undated (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Plenty, Undated (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Plough and the Stars, Undated (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Poor Bitos, Undated (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Poor Murderer, Undated (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Porch, Undated (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Porgy/Porgy and Bess, Undated (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Potting Shed, Undated (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Portrait of Jennie, Undated (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Prague Spring, Undated (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Prayer for My Daughter, Undated (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Prelude to a Kiss, Undated (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Premise, Undated (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Present Laughter, Undated (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Price, Undated (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Prime of Miss Jean Brodie, Undated (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Prisoner of Second Avenue, Undated (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Private Ear and the Public Eye, Undated (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Private Lives, Undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Prodigal, Undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Prodigal Sister, Undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Promenade All, Undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Promise, Undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Promises, Promises, Undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Proposition, Undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - P.S. Your Cat is Dead!, Undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Pump Boys and Dinettes, Undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Puntila and (Matti) His Hired Hand, Undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Purlie Victorious/Purlie, Undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Purple Dust, Undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Pursuit of Happiness, Undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Put Them All Together, Undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Pygmalion, Undated (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Q, 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Q, 1960s-1990s (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Quartermaine's Terms, Undated (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Queen and the Rebels, Undated (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Quills, Undated (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Quilters, Undated (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - R, Undated (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - R, 1919 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - R, 1920s (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - R, 1930s (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - R, 1940s (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - R, 1950s (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - R (file 1 of 2), 1960s (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - R (file 2 of 2), 1960s (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - R (file 1 of 2), 1970s (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - R (file 2 of 2), 1970s (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - R (file 1 of 2), 1980s (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - R (file 2 of 2), 1980s (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - R, 1990s (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - R, 2000s (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Rags, Undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Raggedy Ann, Undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Rain, Undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Rainbow, Undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Rainmaker, Undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Raisin in the Sun/Raisin, Undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Rat Race, Undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Real Estate, Undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Real Inspector Hound, Undated (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Real Thing, Undated (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Reason We Eat, Undated (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Rebecca, Undated (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Reckless, Undated (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Recruiting Officer, Undated (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Red Mill, Undated (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Red Roses for Me, Undated (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Redhead, Undated (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Regard of Flight, Undated (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Rehearsal, Undated (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Relatively Speaking, Undated (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Reluctant Debutante, Undated (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Remains to Be Seen, Undated (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Rent, Undated (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Repertory Theatre of Lincoln Center, Undated (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Requiem for a Heavyweight, Undated (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Resistible Rise of Arturo Ui, Undated (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Rex, Undated (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Rhinoceros, Undated (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Rich and Famous, Undated (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Richard II, Undated (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Richard III, Undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Ride a Black Horse, Undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - River Niger, Undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Riverwind, Undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Right You Are…, Undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Ring Round the Moon, Undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Rink, Undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Rio Rita, Undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Rip Van Winkle, Undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Ritz, Undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Rivals, Undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Road to Mecca, Undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Road to Rome, Undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Roar of the Greasepaint-Smell of the Crowd, Undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Robber Bridegroom, Undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Roberta, Undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Rock-A-Bye Daddy, Undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Rocky Horror Show, Undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Rodgers and Hart, Undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Romance Language, Undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Romanoff and Juliet, Undated (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Romantic Comedy, Undated (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Romeo and Jeanette, Undated (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Romeo and Juliet, Undated (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Romulus, Undated (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Room Service, Undated (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Rosa, Undated (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Rosalie, Undated (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Rosalinda, Undated (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Rose-Marie, Undated (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Rose Tattoo, Undated (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Rosencrantz and Guildenstern are Dead, Undated (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Rosmersholm, Undated (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Rothschilds, Undated (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Rough Crossing, Undated (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Round and Round the Garden, Undated (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Royal Family, Undated (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Royal Gambit, Undated (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Royal Hunt of the Sun, Undated (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Royal Shakespeare Company, Undated (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Roza, Undated (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Ruddigore, Undated (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Rules of the Game, Undated (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Ruling Class, Undated (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Rumors, Undated (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Runaways, Undated (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Runner Stumbles, Undated (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - S, Undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - S, 1910s (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - S (file 1 of 2), 1920s (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - S (file 2 of 2), 1920s (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - S (file 1 of 3), 1930s (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - S (file 2 of 3), 1930s (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - S (file 3 of 3), 1930s (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - S (file 1 of 2), 1940s (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - S (file 2 of 2), 1940s (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - S (file 1 of 3), 1950s (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - S (file 2 of 3), 1950s (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - S (file 3 of 3), 1950s (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - S (file 1 of 4), 1960s (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - S (file 2 of 4), 1960s (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - S (file 3 of 4), 1960s (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - S (file 3 of 4), 1960s (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - S (file 1 of 4), 1970s (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - S (file 2 of 4), 1970s (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - S (file 3 of 4), 1970s (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - S (file 3 of 4), 1970s (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - S (file 1 of 5), 1980s (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - S (file 2 of 5), 1980s (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - S (file 3 of 5), 1980s (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - S (file 4 of 5), 1980s (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - S (file 5 of 5), 1980s (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - S (file 1 of 3), 1990s (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - S (file 2 of 3), 1990s (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - S (file 3 of 3), 1990s (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - S, 2000s (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Sabrina Fair, Undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Saint Joan, Undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Saint Michael's Playhouse, Undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Sally, Undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Same Time, Next Year, Undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Sand Castles, Undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Sarafina!, Undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Satchmo, Undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Saturday Night, Undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Saturday Sunday Monday, Undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Saved, Undated (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Saving Grace, Undated (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Say Darling, Undated (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Say When, Undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Sayonara, Undated (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Scapino, Undated (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Scarlet Letter, Undated (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Scenes from American Life, Undated (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Scenes from an Execution, Undated (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - School for Scandal, Undated (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - School for Wives, Undated (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Schweyk in the Second World War, Undated (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Scrambled Feet, Undated (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Scuba Duba, Undated (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Sea Marks, Undated (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Seagull, Undated (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Seagulls Over Sorrento, Undated (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Season's Greetings, Undated (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Seattle Repertory Theatre, Undated (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Second Avenue Rag, Undated (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Secret Garden, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Secretary Bird, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Seduced, Undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Seesaw, Undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Semi-Detached, Undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Separate Tables, Undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Serenading Louis, Undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Serious Money, Undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Servant of Two Masters, Undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Sesame Street Live!, Undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Seven Brides for Seven Brothers, Undated (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Seven Guitars, Undated (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Seven Year Itch, Undated (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - 1776, Undated (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Seventh Heaven, Undated (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - 70, Girls, 70, Undated (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Shadow Box, Undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Shadow of a Gunman, Undated (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Shadowlands, Undated (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Shay, Undated (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Shayna Maidel, Undated (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - She Also Dances, Undated (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - She Loves Me, Undated (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - She Stoops to Conquer, Undated (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Shear Madness, Undated (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Shelter, Undated (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Shenandoah, Undated (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Sherlock Holmes, Undated (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Sherlock Holmes and the Curse of the Sign of Four, Undated (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Sherlock's Last Case, Undated (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Shirley Valentine, Undated (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Shlemiel the First, Undated (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Sh?gun The Musical, Undated (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Show Boat, Undated (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Show Me Where the Good Times Are, Undated (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Show-Off, Undated (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Showdown at the Adobe Motel, Undated (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Shrike, Undated (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Side by Side by Sondheim, Undated (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Sight Unseen, Undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Sign in Sidney Brustein's Window, Undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Signalmen's Apprentice, Undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Silence, Cunning, Exile, Undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Silver Whistle, Undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Singin' in the Rain, Undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Sister Mary Ignatius Explains It All for You and The Actor's Nightmare, Undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Sisters Rosensweig, Undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Six Characters in Search of an Author, Undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Six Degrees of Separation, Undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Sizwe Banzi is Dead and The Island, Undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Skin of Our Teeth, Undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Slavs! (Thinking about the Longstanding Problems of Virtue and Happiness), Undated (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Sleep of Prisoners, Undated (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Sleuth, Undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Slow Dance on the Killing Ground, Undated (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Sly Fox, Undated (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Small Family Business, Undated (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Smile, Undated (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Smilin' Through, Undated (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Smoke and Mirrors, Undated (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Smoke on the Mountain, Undated (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Smokey Joe's Café, Undated (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Snow Orchid, Undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs, Undated (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - So Long on Lonely Street, Undated (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Solomon's Child, Undated (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Someone Who'll Watch Over Me, Undated (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Something for the Boys, Undated (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Something More, Undated (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Something's Afoot, Undated (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Song and Dance, Undated (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Song of Norway, Undated (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Song of Singapore, Undated (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Sons O' Fun, Undated (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Sophie, Undated (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Sophisticated Ladies, Undated (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Sorrow Beyond Dreams, Undated (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Sorrows of Frederick, Undated (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Sorrows of Stephen, Undated (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Sound of Hunting, Undated (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Sound of Music, Undated (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - South Pacific, Undated (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - Spaulding Gray, Undated (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Speed of Darkness, Undated (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Spofford, Undated (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Spoils of War, Undated (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - Spoon River Anthology, Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Spread Eagle: Son of, IV, Papers, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Spunk, Undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Squabbles, Undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - S. S. Glencairn, Undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Stag at Bay, Undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Stage Door, Undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Stage Struck, Undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Star Spangled Girl, Undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Stardust, Undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Starlight Express, Undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Stars in the Morning Sky, Undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Starting Here, Starting Now, Undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - State Fair, Undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - State of the Union, Undated (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Steel Magnolias, Undated (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Sticks and Bones, Undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Still Life, Undated (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Stop the World-I Want to Get Off, Undated (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Story Theatre, Undated (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Strange Interlude, Undated (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Strange Snow, Undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Strangers, Undated (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Stratford Festival of Canada, Undated (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Streamers, Undated (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Streetcar Named Desire, Undated (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Street Scene, Undated (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Strictly Dishonorable, Undated (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Strider, Undated (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Strike Up the Band, Undated (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Student Prince, Undated (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Sty of the Blind Pig, Undated (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Subject Was Roses, Undated (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Substance of Fire, Undated (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Suds, Undated (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Sugar, Undated (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Sugar Babies, Undated (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Sullivan and Gilbert, Undated (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Sum of Us, Undated (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Summer, Undated (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Summer and Smoke, Undated (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Summer Brave, Undated (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Summer of the Seventeenth Doll, Undated (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - Summerfolk, Undated (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - Sunday in the Park with George, Undated (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Sunrise at Campobello, Undated (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - Sunset, Undated (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Sunset Blvd., Undated (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Sunshine, Undated (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - Sunshine Boys, Undated (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - Sunny, Undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Survival of St. Joan, Undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Survivor, Undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Susan and God, Undated (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Suzanna and the Elders, Undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Swan, Undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Sweeney Todd, Undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Sweet Adeline, Undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Sweet Bird of Youth, Undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Sweet Charity, Undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Sweet Feet, Undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Sweethearts, Undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Swinging on a Star, Undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Sylvia, Undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - T, Undated (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - T, 1915 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - T, 1920s (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - T (file 1 of 2), 1930s (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - T (file 2 of 2), 1930s (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - T (file 1 of 2), 1940s (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - T (file 2 of 2), 1940s (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - T (file 1 of 2), 1950s (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - T (file 2 of 2), 1950s (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - T (file 1 of 3), 1960s (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - T (file 2 of 3), 1960s (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - T (file 3 of 3), 1960s (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - T (file 1 of 2), 1970s (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - T (file 2 of 2), 1970s (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - T (file 1 of 3), 1980s (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - T (file 2 of 3), 1980s (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - T (file 3 of 3), 1980s (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - T (file 1 of 2), 1990s (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - T (file 2 of 2), 1990s (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - T, 2000s (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Table Manners, Undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Take a Giant Step, Undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Take Care, Undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Take Me Along, Undated (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Take My Wife, Undated (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Taken in Marriage, Undated (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Tale of Two Cities, Undated (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Talent ('49, '54, '58, '59, '6-, '61, '64, '65), Undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Tales from the Vienna Woods, Undated (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Tales of the Lost Formicans, Undated (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Talking With, Undated (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Talley's Folly, Undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Tambourines to Glory, Undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Tamburlaine the Great, Undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Taming of the Shrew, Undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Tango, Undated (Box 48, Folder 5)